AUSTIN DREOSCH

Software Developer







React



NextJS







MongoDB













Frontend

React.js, Next.js, Vue, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Vite, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Blender Backend

Node.js, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Express, Redux, Flask, Firebase, SQLAlchemy, TypeScript, GitHub, Jest, SQL

Committed entrepreneurial approach to growth and adaptability with strong problem-solving and analytical skills.

Excellent interpersonal skills. Teamplayer who highly values flexible, collaborative culture and creative independent workflows.

Highly motivated and self-driven. Strong attention to detail, and versatile experience working independently.



austindreosch@gmail.com



(+1) 707-308-9486



San Francisco Bay Area, CA



Portfolio

austindreosch.github.io



LinkedIn austindreosch



GitHub

<u>austindreosch</u>

Education



Springboard 2022 - 2024

Software Engineering

Intensive hands-on experience in end-to-end software development principles in multiple programming languages (JavaScript, Python, C#) with technical skills focused on full stack web applications in emerging technologies, data structures & algorithms, asynchronous dynamic programming, APIs, testing, troubleshooting & C.S. fundamentals.



Sonoma State University

General Studies, Bachelor's

Graduated with my Bachelor's in a broad multidisciplinary program focused around critical thinking, mathematics, art, science, literature, communication, and problem solving.

Latest projects







prep kitchen A healthy meal delivered to your door, every single day.

Playbook Al

Fantasy sports toolkit. Organized sports data visualization. Multiple data streams demonstrating complex API manipulation with cloud data integration on NoSQL database solution. Vercel as deployment platform to ensure performance and reliability.









Quillwind Al

Generative Al tool Solution for roducing custom SEO-optimized blog pieces through my integration with OpenAl API, SAAS web application with Stripe integration, frontend in React JS, secure user authentication with authO, RESTful APIs, UI/UX design in Tailwind CSS, full-stack app showing proficiency in diverse web app technologies.





Prep Kitchen

A meal delivery service app. Demonstrating full-stack Python development through jQuery and integration of the MealDB API. Python (Flask) backend with Postgres data storage and retrieval, OOP, REST, fully handmade UI design with CSS3, HTML5. Flask Jinja and SQLAlchemy ORM for interfacing with back-end data.







Summary

Self-motivated full-stack developer with 5+ years of independent project experience coupled with a comprehensive formal education in software engineering and a bachelors degree from Sonoma State University. Expertise in full-stack development across multiple languages (JavaScript, Python, C#), toolsets and paradigms. Greatest strengths are an undying appetite for new skills, learning and rapid improvement. Exceptional softskills candidate - gifted communicator, highly professional and bright spirited attitude.

Experience

March 2023 - Present 9 St. Helena, CA



Marketing / Design / Admin

Engel & Völkers

March 2022 - January 2023 Q Austin, TX



Workplace Coordinator **CBRE**

- Led development and coordination of all marketing materials. design innovation, and client presentations for top Napa real estate agent with annual sales volume exceeding \$200,000,000.
- Took on leadership responsibilities with junior employees, interns and led team building and office collaboration.
- · Managed all employee-facing services, and communication between clients, vendors, and staff for the Austin, TX branch of the world's largest commercial real estate firm.
- · Contributed in the production and implementation of marketing materials and branded campaigns.
- · Independently managed supply chain tasks and event coordination with high-profile clients.